### LINKS

#### Portfolio:

https://ckapsalis2710.github.io/ portfolio/

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/c hristos-kapsalis-lin/

### GitHub:

https://github.com/ckapsalis27

<u>10</u>

### **ABOUT ME**

### **Full-stack software**

developer for 8+ years in numerous software projects. Front-end development in

Javascript, React, CSS, Bootstrap and HTML. Backend development in Java, Lua and **PHP**. Eager to learn new languages, technologies and undertake interesting projects. Accountable, working on schedule and comfortable working as a team member.

### **SKILLS**

JAVASCRIPT/ REACT/ JQUERY/ HTML/ CSS/ **BOOTSTRAP** 

JAVA/ LUA/ PHP/ C/ SQL/ **BASH SCRIPTING** 

NODEJS/ EXPRESSJS

**KUBERNETES/ DOCKERS** 

XML/JSON/AJAX/SVI

GIT/SVN

ROBOT/JENKINS

**REGULAR EXPRESSIONS** 

VS CODE/ ECLIPSE (+SPRING FRAMEWORK)/ PHPSTORM/ **CODECHARGE STUDIO** 

SQL CLIENTS (PGADMIN4, DBEAVER, DB VISUALIZER. DB BROWSER FOR SQLITE, NAVICAT)

POSTMAN/ WIRESHARK

**BROWSERS' WEB** 

**BALSAMIC (MOCK-UPS)** 

**AGILE** 

**CMS** 

WINDOWS & LINUX OS

## LANGUAGES

GREEK

ENGLISH

**ITALIAN** 

### **HOBBIES**

HIKING/CLIMBING/SKI-SNOWBOARD/ TAEKWONDO/ **SWIMMING** 

# **CHRISTOS KAPSALIS**



+306947934771

xrikapsalis@gmail.com

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Nov 2022 - Present

**Sabbatical - Freelance Climbing Instructor** 

### **NOKIA**

Athens Dec 2021 - Oct 2022

### **Senior Technical Specialist**

- Back-end development of Altiplano Controller, an open software GUI platform that served as an API to connect other Nokia's software units.
- Software development of a feature in **Java**, tested on JUnit, loaded on a **Docker** container, deployed on Kubernetes platform. Most of the work applied to arrange PODs configuration and their software interaction, under Kubernetes.
- Experience in Intent development logic, Microservices, Cloud based solutions, DevOps operations, Kibana search engine, Postman request engine.

### NOKIA

Athens Sep 2016 - Dec 2021

### **Software Engineer**

- Full-stack development of WebCT, a software that provided a GUI to administer X-Haul microwave products.
- · Back-end development of WebCT in **Lua** and DB handling with Lua-Sqlite3. As well, development in Java with JUnit testing of ASLM, an app that produces licenses for all X-Haul products.
- · Front-end development in Javascript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS, and Bootstrap framework.
- · Involved with the full circle of a feature's production. Creation and reviewing of features' code, software architectural designs, Low Level Design, mock-ups, CuDo documents. Developing at least one feature per release while following a biannual release schedule.
- · Peer reviewing of Code, Use Cases, Test Strategy and Test Cases.
- · Full stack Unit Testing and debugging code.

#### NOKIA

Athens Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

### **Software Engineer**

- Full-stack software development of the FMANG application, managing Nokia's FlexiNG product. An app that offered mainly a GUI to monitor all kind of alarms, statistics and product's health, like also managing all kind of product's configuration.
- · Back-end development in Java and Java EE Development toolset: JSF/Primefaces, Spring, Hibernate, Maven, Tomcat, Jenkins, Junit.
- · Front-end development in Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- · Change the whole product's GUI style after company's rebranding. Create some new features, debugging and peer reviewing of code. Milestone, to solve with the help of the team a crucial bug that maid the whole app to fail.

#### **NOKIA** Athens

Oct 2014 - May 2015

### **E&V Tester**

- · Responsible for CI Test suite of Nokia's LTE network gateway (FlexiNG) of around 400 Test Cases.
- Entity and Verification testing in **Robot** framework. Daily report on the CI state and fixing each TC that failed.
- · Enhancing the CI by creating some new TCs.

#### **CYBERTECHNICS** INTERACTIVE COMMUNICATION LTD

Athens Dec 2012 - Jan 2014

### Web Programmer/Developer

- Full-stack software development of Modus CMS.
- Back-end development in **PHP** and DB handling with MySQL. Front-end development in Javascript, HTML, CSS.
- · Responsible for Back-end administration and development of Modus CMS.
- Updating and debugging CMS' code. Creating CMS' modules, components, droplets. Data handling through DB queries of production's applications, upon customers requests.
- Implementation of RAFM (Restricted Access File Manager) filesystem and integration of Ajaxplorer GUI into Modus CMS.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **UNIVERSITY OF PIRAEUS** Piraeus

2011

**University Degree in Digital Systems & Technology Education: Informatics** 

#### **STOCKHOLM UNIVERSITY AND KTH JOINT DEPARTMENT**

Stockholm 2009

**COURSE** 

**Erasmus Exchange Student Program: Knowledge** Management

### **ZERO TO MASTERY**

**ACADEMY** Sep 2024 - Present

Fullstack Web Developer Career Path. Updating my knowledge on CSS, latest versions of Javascript, learning REACT, NodeJS with ExpressJS, PostgreSQL by building a full-stack app and using a Machine Learning API.